Ezio Martinelli Papers
Ezio Martinelli Papers
- Memorabilia
  - Miscellany (Box 11)
United States Information Agency 1961 Mar. 10 1961 Mar. 14 (outgoing typescript photocopy) 1961 Apr. 13 1961 Apr. 20 (outgoing typescript carbon) 1967 June 7
Von Erffa, Helmut 1939 Sept. 20 1945 Mar. 25 1945 May 19 1947 May 11 1947 Sept. 12 1947 Oct. 2 1948 Jan. 23 1948 Feb. 8 1948 Feb. 10 1948 Feb. 17 1949 Nov. 18 1952 June 16 1956 May 30 1957 May 20 1957 Oct. 8 1957 Dec. 5 1958 June 9 1958 June 21 (outgoing typescript photocopy) 1958 July 16 1958 Nov. 7 1962 Sept. 30 undated
Whitney Museum of American Art 1955 Apr. 12 1955 Apr. 25 (outgoing typescript carbon) 1956 June 26 1958 Apr. 23 (outgoing typescript photocopy) 1959 Feb. 17 1960 May 6 (outgoing typescript carbon) 1960 May 13 1966 Nov. 18 undated (outgoing typescript photocopy)
Willard Gallery (New York City) 1945 May 28 1945 June 1 (outgoing typescript carbon) 1945 June 5 (outgoing typescript carbon) 1945 June 14 1945 June (?) (outgoing typescript carbon) 1945 Oct. 9 (outgoing typescript carbon) 1945 Nov. 14 1945 Dec. 3 (outgoing typescript carbon) 1945 Dec. 6 1945 Dec. 17 (outgoing typescript carbon) 1946 Jan. 24 (outgoing typescript carbon) 1946 Jan. 30 1946 Feb. 2 (outgoing typescript carbon) 1946 Feb. 28 1946 Mar. 4 (outgoing typescript carbon) 1946 Apr. 17 (outgoing typescript carbon) 1946 Apr. 18 1946 Apr. 22 (outgoing typescript carbon) 1946 May 17 1946 May 23 (outgoing typescript carbon) 1946 June 10 (outgoing typescript carbon) 1946 June 17 (outgoing typescript carbon) 1946 June 20 1946 June 28 (outgoing typescript carbon) 1946 Oct. 14 1946 Nov. 13 1946 Nov. 17 (outgoing typescript photocopy) 1946 Dec. 12 1946 Dec. 15 (outgoing typescript photocopy) 1947 Jan. 8 (outgoing typescript photocopy) 1947 Jan. 10 1947 Jan. 15 (outgoing typescript carbon) 1947 Jan. 21 1947 Jan. 30 (outgoing typescript carbon) 1947 Feb. 1 1947 Feb. 5 1947 Feb. 11 (outgoing typescript carbon) 1947 Mar. 21 (outgoing typescript carbon) 1947 Mar. 25 1947 Mar. 31 (outgoing typescript carbon) 1947 Apr. 18 1947 May 3 1947 July 23 1947 Oct. 20 1947 Dec. 19 1948 Oct. 7 1949 Feb. 14 1950 Oct. 24 1954 June 11 (postcard) 1954 July 16 (postcard) 1955 Oct. 25 (from Art in America) 1956 Nov. 29 (carbon to Henry Allen Moe re: Guggenheim fellowship) 1958 June 27 1958 July 6 (outgoing typescript photocopy) 1958 Aug. 2 1958 Sept. 18 1958 Oct. 9 (postcard) 1958 Nov. 7 (from the Museum of Fine Arts of Houston) 1959 Jan. 7 (carbon from the Museum of Fine Arts of Houston) undated (8 items) See also Memorabilia: Art Associations
Willis, Betty 1947 Apr. 2 (gallery sale)
Wollowick, David P. 1964 May 4 1964 May 4 (outgoing typescript carbon) 1964 May 21 1964 May 26 (outgoing typescript carbon) 1964 June 14 (outgoing typescript carbon) 1964 June (?)
Young, Mahonri Sharp 1953 Feb. 17
Zigrosser, Carl 1956 Mar. 15 (outgoing typescript carbon) 1956 Mar. 21 1956 Mar. 29 1961 Sept. 25 (outgoing typescript carbon)